dramanetwork.net 2013-12-14

# Privacy statement | Island School

**Privacy Policy  ** **私隱政策**

The English Schools Foundation (ESF) and its schools collect and hold personal information of individuals for various purposes. ESF and its schools are committed to meeting internationally recognised standards of personal data privacy protection, in compliance with the requirements of the [Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance](http://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/ordinance/ordglance.html). In doing so, it will be ensured that ESF staff and any parties who are assigned by ESF to handle the information will comply with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.  Unless permitted or required by law, ESF and its schools will not disclose any personal data to any third parties without prior written consent. 

Under the Ordinance, users have the right to request access to and correction of their personal data held. Should you wish to access or correct your personal information held by ESF or its schools, please send your request by email to [info@esfcentre.edu.hk](mailto:info@esfcentre.edu.hk).  

There are three general categories of personal data held by ESF and its schools:

1.     **Student information** , which includes information supplied by students / parents and is collected in connection with student applications, student records, former students, contacts and communications activities undertaking by or on behalf of ESF and its schools. Student records are kept for purposes that include corresponding with, responding to and taking follow-up actions in respect of students, contacts and communications activities.

2.     **Personnel information** , which includes personal particulars, job descriptions, details of compensation and benefits, performance appraisals, references and disciplinary matters relating to job applicants, employees and former employees of ESF and its schools. Personnel records of employees are kept for human resource management purposes, relating to such matters as employees’ terms of employment, performance appraisal, providing references, professional development, discipline and termination.

3.     **Other records** , which include administration and other files, containing personal data provided to ESF and its schools by individuals for purposes other than those connected with students, contacts, communications or employment.   Other records are kept to enable ESF and its schools to carry out various functions and activities which vary according to the nature of the purpose for which such records are to be used, including the administration of ESF’s and its schools’ functions and activities, seeking advice on operational matters, undertaking communications and training activities organised by, or on behalf of, ESF and its schools, including the acquisition of services and handling of enquiries from members of the public.

The phrase “English Schools Foundation (ESF) and its schools” means ESF Centre, the fifteen schools operated by ESF, the two Private Independent Schools and the four kindergartens operated under ESF Educational Services Limited (ESL).

If you have any queries about our policy and practices, please write to [info@esfcentre.edu.hk](mailto:info@esfcentre.edu.hk).  

This privacy policy statement has been translated into Chinese. If there is any inconsistency or ambiguity between the English version and the Chinese version, the English version shall prevail.

May 2011
